I'm meeting Hal, so I've dressed up as hard as I can? She's cute.
Sorry to interrupt.
Long time no see.
Are you nervous?
I'm super nervous.
More nervous than I've ever been in my life.
I'm really nervous.
I swear to God, I'm lying.
Oh, my God.
At least let me show you a lot more, Alba.
This video is about a man who eats rice with a wet noodle.
This video is brought to you by Nukumeshi, who eats his food in a warm and comfortable way.
Kinijan, let's order the menu.
I don't know what to order.
Have you eaten? Lunch.
No, I didn't have lunch.
You haven't eaten? Just breakfast.
We're the same.
You've been eating less in the morning for this, haven't you? Did you eat a hamburger?
I've already eaten a hamburger.
We ate hamburgers.
Forget it.
Just have Sala and pork miso soup.
That's amazing.
Then I can have both, sweet and savoury.
I can eat a lot of rice, too.
Want some, Maru-chan?
I just had breakfast.
I'm hungry. I can eat.
You don't eat much?
I'll eat.
Do all orcas eat?
They all eat a lot.
I get that a lot.
I eat a lot.
They eat everything when it's on the table.
I'll eat it when it comes out.
They're going to eat it. - Aikemon and the others also receive gifts at one-man shows, and at the end we each put a small gift in a rather large bag.
Go on, go on, go on...
That's more like...
Like three bags.
That's right.
This is how we bring them home.
Let's order first.
What do you want to drink?
I'm so indecisive, I don't know.
I don't know.
Homemade lemonade sounds good.
Oh, that sounds delicious.
It's so good.
Wait, what time is it?
You can have the lunch menu.
What?
Not this?
Definitely that one.
I saw someone eating something off the menu.
Someone who ate it.
This one's good.
This one.
I think I'll have this.
And there's a drink included, so everyone eats a big lunch.
It's so good, everyone will eat a big lunch.
This looks really good. Omelette?
Sinzer salad.
This is the omelette plate.
Omelette plate?
Wait, I can't!
Looks delicious.
Yummy, yummy, yummy, hahaha, the plum looks good, too.
All right, go on.
New Yorker pancakes!
That's how you cheat on me.
You don't eat sweet pancakes?
Well, you know what?
Go, go, go, go, go, go, go, go, go, go, go, go.
Boom, boom, boom.
What? Laughs. - He eats more and more. - Is it good at all? Can you? - Yeah, I can do it. It's fine, it's fine, he eats a lot, so it's fine.
We'll have a side dish for each of us.
We'll see about the sweet ones.
But we'll have to order one of each.
Yeah, let's do it.
Pancakes are a possibility?
Yeah, I think so.
I want pancakes so bad.
That looks good.
They look good, don't they?
And there's an egg on top.
I want an omelette.
I want to eat this and this.
I'll eat this and this.
I love the flower library. I want to eat everything.
I love the Ohana Bunko. I want to eat it all.
I'm not your sister...
I want an older brother too.
I want an elder brother too, then we've all done it, Maeda!
This doesn't make any sense. You're a cat! Yumeko and my brother are the same age... two of them... two of them...
I want to play!
It's fun, fun, fun!
Then this one, this one and this one.
Is there another one you'd like to eat in reverse? Pasta?
Sure, pasta.
Let's try it again.
Yeah, sure.
Crab? Walleye.
Walleye.
I'll get the keys.
Excuse me, sir.
May I?
New York pancakes and truffle omelette plate from the lunch menu.
Truffle omelette plate.
and
Pasta with crab in tomato cream, please.
I'd like a drink.
Apple and
Oolong tea and
Iced latte.
Please, please, please, oolong tea and an iced latte.
But I'll save it.
I have something sweet.
It's okay.
Okay.
Okinawan long time? - Okinawan long time.
Surprisingly, it doesn't look like Sasuburi.
Surprisingly, it fits.
It fits!
Like I said before, it fits.
Surprisingly, it fits!
At the end of the year, it was the Momoshiki Uta Gassen.
From then on, the Okinawan stars were short.
It's an Okinawan concept.
Wow!
Thank you very much.
I wish we could have talked more in Okinawa.
I wish we could have talked more in Okinawa, that's for sure.
That's for sure.
Indeed.
I wanted to see you finally.
Do you all drink?
We're all pretty happy drinking normally.
Oh, I see.
Jayne.
I didn't think it would be such a big change.
I'm usually pretty high.
It's true, Ho-chan won't change, but I don't think she'll change, because she's usually pretty high.
You won't change?
Really?
Surprising!
You're so strong!
I love you so much!
Ho-chan nappies?
I'm really not changing.
I really won't change.
It'll always be like that.
It's always been like...
It's like, "Wow.
Wow, that's great.
It's probably too much alcohol.
Well, if it's as good as it tastes, I'll just have a soft drink.
You can go for a yes... soft drink yes.
Who would be the most unusual yes?
But...
I don't know... there's no type of person who becomes easy all the time...
Yuzuki, I think it's easy to see that you've come around.
Nao and Haru make me sleepy.
Oh, how cute!
So be careful not to drink too much, on the other hand, because it makes you sleepy.
I see.
Yuzuki is easy to recognise when she comes in.
It's like, 'Oh, it's coming round'.
I wanted to drink so much.
Maybe I should go out for a drink.
I want to drink.
Let's go, let's go.
After 26 February.
That's right. Whenever you can.
It'll definitely be fun.
A fun one?
The flowers I'm interested in.
Yes, they are.
I wonder what they'll be like.
I have no idea.
Iced lattes and...
fashionable
Bourbon tea.
Thank you.
Thank you very much.
Super Ocean.
Let's have a toast.
Hey, hey, hey, hey, hey, hey, hey, hey, hey, hey, hey, hey, hey, hey, hey, hey, hey, hey, hey, hey, hey, hey, hey. Yes, yes, yes.
Yay, cape.
Thank you very much.
It's delicious.
How are you today? How's work?
I've got a lesson later. So what do you normally do from home? I have a lesson later.
So you came from home normally?
Yes, that's right.
I came here for lunch with Haru, as if we were having lunch together.
But we're so alike in that sense.
Haru left today, too.
I left and went home.
On the lesson.
I'm thinking about the choreography for our next new song.
I'll think about the choreography for the next song.
I'm thinking about the choreography for my song, so I'm doing my own choreography.
You do it yourselves?
I've been in charge of the choreography for two or two songs in the past, depending on the song.
I'm going to do one of the songs on the next album.
We've been thinking about it, and now we're here.
I haven't had any conversations with anyone. So I'm not really thinking straight.
Can I ask you to do it again, alone, in the lesson hall?
Is the lesson room free at this time of the day by myself? I asked the manager.
Oh, really?
Wow, that's amazing.
You're so versatile.
Yeah, it would be fun if everyone else did it too.
It would be fun if everyone else did it too.
Oh, I'll never be able to do that.
Do you want to swing it yourself?
I'm sure Ira and the others can do it, but...
I think I can do an aila.
Well, from the members' point of view...
I'm doing my best to do what the teacher taught me.
I'm sure you've thought about it.
It's not like she'd have learned it if she'd gone dancing.
Thank you.
Looks delicious.
Crab-crab.
I want to take a photo.
Let's take a photo.
It smells so good.
Crab!
Oh, my God.
He's taking pictures of crabs.
I know.
He's filming crabs.
You just surprised me with one of your own.
That feels good.
It happens sometimes, doesn't it?
I'm like, "Oh, my God, I'm so surprised.
It's so cute.
It's a permanent fixture.
I'll share the pasta.
Thank you very much.
I want to lose, I want to lose.
When it comes to the members, it's decided who'll do it.
I don't think we have to do it. Yuzu will do it.
Everyone tells me I don't have to do it every time.
No, I'll take it myself, whether I'm eating it or not, so they tell me not to do it.
I'll take it myself.
Who are you? I don't want it.
They say they'll do it themselves.
That's a common thing among the members.
But the killer whales...
Nao or Haru?
Heh...
I get the impression they do it.
But he's the type who says he'll leave it up to others.
But he's the type that says he'll leave it up to you and never do it.
I'm glad you're doing it, because I'd really appreciate it if you'd just serve it to me if I want it.
I'm not sure if it's a good idea to eat it all by yourself, but it's not right.
Then he eats different things one after the other.
One day he wants it all, and then it's too much trouble.
I'm not going to go out for dinner with my seniors...
I don't have it.
Aaryn is the only one.
Aaryn's the only one.
I'm going with Aaryn.
Where do you get the idea to go?
You're the ones who want to go.
But we're the ones who said yes.
It's like, okay. The flowers are pretty supportive.
I see. I'll go, I'll go.
Was it? Was it?
The first time we said let's go, we went too far, I don't remember.
The first time we went to Disney? We were talking about how we wanted to go to Disney together.
I think it was the first time I went to Disney.
The flowers are not in the water, so we go there and shake them.
I'm shaking them, saying thank you, thank you, thank you, thank you.
Thank you very much.
And even the schedule...
We'll go, we'll go, we'll go...
Aaryn's already too good for this.
I'll send you a letter.
He tells me everything.
As expected...
There are people who work when they play.
He's the epitome of that.
It's not a scam or anything.
I'm really available here and here, but...
But the Amefula schedule didn't suit me at all.
I said, "This isn't going to work.
So I asked Aaryn to call us, the Amefla managers.
I asked her to call us.
Arline asked him to give Amefla the day off.
How did that go?
If Aaryn says so.
Aaryn must be amazing.
Bon appétit.
Are you sure you want to eat the crab?
Eat the crab.
How do you do it?
You can't do much more than tinkle around here.
Eating crab pasta is always a challenge.
It's always difficult to eat crab pasta, it's always difficult to eat crab pasta, it's always difficult to eat crab pasta, it's always difficult to eat crab pasta.
Eating crab pasta is always a challenge, isn't it?
The one where you have to split the crab...
It's always a challenge, isn't it?
It's difficult.
You're amazing.
I knew it.
It's delicious.
That's exactly what Universe is like.
It's all Arin's.
Why did you say Universe?
When we talked about how we wanted to go to Universe the next time we went to Disney.
We'd already talked about it then.
Yes, or else it's a junior's plan.
I'm going to connect you by any means necessary.
Yes, I really want to connect it to Yunema.
But it's amazing.
Wow, it looks delicious. Thank you.
The first thing I remember from today.
It's just a picture!
This crab is really real, proper crab.
Delicious!
Okay, Haru, you're getting an omelet.
You there?
It's so cute!
So cute, so cute, the area looks like it's going to be a real treat.
It's not often we get to go to such a stylish place.
So you said we'd go to Unibai too, and you gave us another itinerary? So we decided to go to Unibay too, and they gave us another itinerary?
That's what Arline said, right?
Great! So we'll find a time when we can all fit in two days.
So we'll find a time when we can all fit in two days.
I'm going to Universe with Aaryn.
I'm going to Univa with Aaryn.
I asked her.
If she says...
Where do you need to go?
That's great.
You'll give me a schedule as soon as you go.
You're so dynamic.
The MBTI.
He's a guy with so much stuff.
What are you going to do?
Limottes.
Consulate.
So many different limottes.
You have cake.
What's a consulate?
I don't understand unless you say it in English.
You have to understand.
DN.
Thank you.
Looks good. Thank you.
Oh, no, no, no, no, no, no.
Oh, man.
I'm painting it from here.
ESFJ.
Only one piece different from this one.
That's right.
I want to know about Hana-chan's. ES.
I'm an INFJ.
Like your grandfather.
Yes, yes, yes.
When we were on the radio before, she was a guest with me.
I don't remember what we were talking about, but...
Yuzu-chan said...
Well, Haru-chan...
Suddenly, wait a minute!
What's FBJ? She said.
We're entertainers.
Haru-chan thought, "Wait a minute".
Ha-ha-ha-ha-ha-ha.
They're saying.
Yeah, I see, that's what it is.
You can tell by looking at her, can't you?
I could hear that she was similar to me, that we had the same senses.
And when I asked her, she said we were the same.
That's amazing.
And then Izu-chan said...
Is she an entertainer? She was like that.
You seem like a super entertainer.
They look so much alike.
She came in all hungry, and we thought we were the same.
And then they kept talking.
And then we started talking, and then we started talking, and then we started talking.
They talk a lot and they have the same sense of humour.
With Haru.
Feel it? Entertainment
Entertainment.
I have a feeling...
You feel...
I thought you were a different kind of person.
Oh.
So, are you shy or something?
Not like that?
No, I'm not shy.
But you can talk.
You can talk normally, too.
Yes, I can talk normally.
But I don't blow much.
Hmm...
Osaka.
Maybe it's too late to open here.
That's for sure.
Hmm...
He talks a lot.
But sometimes I feel like I'm open to this person.
It's narrow and deep, isn't it? Really, in the current environment.
Shallow and wide, isn't it?
The difference is that I'm shallow and open as much as possible.
But the deepest ones are really beautiful! It's beauty, isn't it?
Yes, yes, yes.
Let's divide it into three equal parts.
Let's divide it into thirds.
Truffles!
Oh, no!
Truffles...
They smell so good.
You can't eat truffles unless they're at the bottom.
It's true.
Eat it... today.
Pink Rye.
Pancakes.
Oh, yummy.
Oh, my God.
Oh, no. Cracking eggs?
It's difficult, isn't it? What? Cracking eggs? Huh?
It's difficult, isn't it?
But I want to eat it thick.
Here we go.
Ready?
Yeah!
You're not going anywhere.
No?
Yeah, that's not going to work, is it? No? Yeah.
It's not going to work, is it?
No?
Looks good.
Bon appétit.
Looks amazing.
Mmm.
Delicious.
Yum.
Mmm-mmm.
I'm so happy.
Dad, weren't you in it? Something.
I am.
Do you like being out, Dad?
Stop being out.
Stop being a prude.
Ha-ha-ha-ha.
Stop talking.
Oh, are you going to come out?
Woo, woo.
This week,
Suikoo!
Short man-car!
Wait a minute.
Yes, sir.
What's that? You haven't seen it? No, no, no, actually, today we have another special guest.
And for Hana, I've invited someone who'll be a regular on the show, and whom I'd like to meet the most.
There's Ostler, of course... the third one today, right, Star?
Star!
Oh, no...
Stop it!
Don't answer it! Don't answer it!
Suddenly you say sweetness.
Yes, so, Kojima Hana's father.
Don't answer it!
Yeah!
I really don't want to.
I don't want my parents to appear in the world.
They're the most private people in the world.
You know, really private people.
Family?
It's embarrassing.
You don't look anything like your sister.
No resemblance?
No, we don't.
Do I look like her? We're brothers.
I definitely don't look like you.
My dad and my brother.
I'd introduce them as family, but they wouldn't even know.
It's funny.
It's funny, because I probably wouldn't be able to get there today if I didn't introduce my family.
I'm glad you're here, because I've never experienced this.
I've never experienced anything like this.
It's a group of really selfish people... who are all alone... and it feels right.
I don't like it.
I don't know.
It doesn't feel right.
It doesn't feel like an older brother.
It's like a child's mind.
Yes, yes.
That's why we didn't make a leader, because we're all only children.
Hmm...
We talked about whether we should have a leader when we went from five to four.
But I think the most important thing is whether it's Moe or Moe for me.
Moe is good because he's free now, but the older members are the ones who are putting out the most books, so it's like he's the one who's making it happen.
If you put a sense of responsibility on it, the goodness will disappear, maybe the goodness will disappear, and when everyone else does it, it's not the same.
Well, I don't need it.
So they make a leader.
Of course you do.
We don't have a leader.
It's always been decided that Earth and Honoka would be in the centre.
We talked about it a lot at the time when it was just 6, 5 from the beginning and then 4...
But in the end we didn't make it, and now we're thinking about making it again? We talked about it a lot, but in the end we didn't make it, and now we're just thinking about making it.
But in the end we didn't make it.
Did you think about making it?
We talked about making it for a moment, but...
But no! I think it's better not to have it.
Not as a group, but after talking to the staff and Mind...
I think it's better to leave it as it is.
I think I have a weird sense of responsibility.
That's what idols are like, with a leader in the centre.
There's an image that there's a leader in the centre and the members are divided into groups.
If we followed that image...
I don't think it would go well.
I think there might have been a sense of...
Maybe we're a bit like Shaki.
Yeah, we're really similar.
We have a lot in common.
I think we have a lot in common.
Yeah, I think so.
Everyone has their own thing.
It's like one person stands out.
We have different personalities.
But...
Everyone has their own strength.
It brings out their colours.
The group.
Orca, do you have any big goals?
Do you have any big goals?
What are my big goals?
When we were Team Chachioco, we performed at the Budokan twice,
Now that we are four members,
I would like to perform at the Budokan one more time with the current team of Team Shachi,
Last summer, we performed at Nagoya Castle, Shachi-sama,
Nagoya Castle was where we started as Chachioco,
It was very hard to perform at Corona, and we couldn't do any live shows,
We had such a situation, but our centre said again that we are going to start again from this summer, as a dream.
Hou-chan said it again, and she also reiterated the goal for all of us.
We're sitting in the Budokan now, so we're in the middle of the tour.
We're going to go to a lot of places.
It's really cool, even though it's quick.
Fun, fun, fun, fun, fun, fun, fun, fun, fun, fun, fun.
Fun, fun, fun.
There's always really cool, fun, fun, fun, fun.
It's always there.
Come on, just like that, the singing contest, the Staplefest, just like that, just like that, the Amefura and the killer whales were lined up!
I'm sure they're standing in line.
They were standing side by side!
And because they have completely different colours, when they stand side by side, you know what I mean?
I can see that.
It's not a synergy effect, but...
But they work well together.
That's what all this Okinawan talk is about.
That's what I was thinking when I was talking with the members.
I was thinking that a lot.
You guys have great chemistry.
Before and after Shaki, it's like Sha...
It's different when it's a cute group.
The Japs...
The synergy is amazing.
It's like they're totally different colours, but there's a strong difference in the different ones.
Something a bit different but similar.
I'm glad there are people like that.
They really do look alike.
I'm glad we talked once today.
It's really private, everyone.
I'd like to go out with you in private.
I have your contact details, so please share them with us.
You should definitely exchange them.
You should definitely exchange.
Entertainer channel.
Definitely exchange.
Share what?
It's just too much trouble.
It's getting more and more complicated if you ask me to share it with you.
I'll never do that.
We exchanged contact details right after that.
I would never do that.
I won't do it.
Every time I tell her to tell me where she sleeps.
He never comes.
Oh, no.
I'll do it right after.
And I didn't get to eat your panties today.
I really didn't.
I'll have some panties.
And then you can eat her.
Eat her.
And then we'll both pay, but that's okay.
I'm going home.
Take care, everyone.
I couldn't rest.
This video was sent to you by Nukumeshi, who eats his dinner in peace.
This video was sent to you by Nukumeshi.